<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="difficult_ans">

        <item>It is an open-sourced operating system that is used primarily on mobile devices, such as cell phones and tablets. It is a Linux kernel-based system that been equipped with rich components that allows developers to create and run apps that can perform both basic and advanced functions.</item>
        <item>The Google Android SDK is a toolset that developers need in order to write apps on Android enabled devices. It contains a graphical interface that emulates an Android driven handheld environment, allowing them to test and debug their codes.</item>
        <item>Android Architecture is made up of 4 key components:
        1	Linux Kernel
        2	Libraries
        3	Android Framework
        4	Android Applications
        </item>
        <item>The Android Framework is an important aspect of the Android Architecture. Here you can find all the classes and methods that developers would need in order to write applications on the Android environment.</item>
        <item>AAPT is short for Android Asset Packaging Tool. This tool provides developers with the ability to deal with zip-compatible archives, which includes creating, extracting as well as viewing its contents.</item>
        <item>The emulator lets developers "play" around an interface that acts as if it were an actual mobile device. They can write and test codes, and even debug. Emulators are a safe place for testing codes especially if it is in the early design phase.</item>
        <item>An activityCreator is the first step towards the creation of a new Android project. It is made up of a shell script that will be used to create new file system structure necessary for writing codes within the Android IDE.</item>
        <item>Activities are what you refer to as the window to a user interface. Just as you create windows in order to display output or to ask for an input in the form of dialog boxes, activities play the same role, though it may not always be in the form of a user interface.</item>
        <item>Intents displays notification messages to the user from within the Android enabled device. It can be used to alert the user of a particular state that occurred. Users can be made to respond to intents.</item>
        <item>Activities can be closed, or terminated anytime the user wishes. On the other hand, services are designed to run behind the scenes, and can act independently. Most services run continuously, regardless of whether there are certain or no activities being executed.</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>